VU DANG ANH DAO

MEDICAL REPRESENTATIVE

184 Dien Hong Street, Ward 1, Binh Thanh District, HCMC.

Tel: (+84) 38 274 5278

Email: anhdaoyds@gmail.com

Representative Office
BAXTER HEALTHCARE (ASIA PACIFIC) PTE. LTD IN VIETNAM
Room 1008, Floor 10, Diamond Plaza, 34 Le Duan Street, Ben Nghe Ward, District 1, HCMC.

Dear Sir/Madam,

I have recently seen recruitment information from your company about medical representative and I really care about that position.

I have just graduated from University of Medicine and Pharmacy, HCMC. I am a pharmacist and business is my passion. That's the reason why in 5 years in university, I've become the sales man in some shops and started 2 online shops by my own. In the journey of doing business, after so many of failure as well as success, I believe that now I have some certain experiences in sales, dealing with people, marketing and problem - solving skill.

Besides, I participated in a club at my high school for two years. It has helped me a lot in developing my communication ability and teamwork skill.

I am an active person and always have positive critical thinking when it comes to complicated situations. With the skills and the experiences that I have while I was studying, working, I ensure I can be an effective and energetic MR as well as working well under pressure. I might not be the best, but I will do my best to enhance the society health and from then, contribute to the increase in revenue and customers of your company.

Thank you for the time spending on this letter. I truly hope that you can arrange an interview, so I can express more about myself directly as well as better understand about the requirements for MR.

Yours sincerely, Vu Dang Anh Dao



VU DANG ANH DAO

MEDICAL REPRESENTATIVE

184 Dien Hong Street, Ward 1, Binh Thanh District, HCMC

Tel: (+84) 38 274 5278

Email: anhdaoyds@gmail.com

EDUCATION

University of Medicine and Pharmacy, HCMC.

2013 - 2018

Pharmacist

CAREER OBJECTIVE

- In the first month, study and understand the product's value, learn about the area and start building relationships.
- After 2-months of working, continously practise and enhance the necessary knowledge, skills for MR, can work independently, achieve the targets set by the company.
- Within three to five years, I'm looking for ward to work in marketing field.

| 0 | v | - 1 | |
|-----|---|---------|--|
| . 7 | n | | |

- Teamworking
- Communication
- Sales
- · Problem sovling
- Negotiation skills

STRENGTHS

- Flexibility
- Positive Thinking
- Enthusiasm
- Independence

HOBBIES

- Travelling
- Reading
- Fashion

WORK EXPERIENCE

Oct 2013 - Present

PRIVATE TUTOR

- Teach Math, Physics and Chemistry
- Presentation skills

Feb 2015 - Dec 2015

AO DAI HANH

Part - time executive

- Strengthen communication and consultancy skill for consumers
- Problem solving skill and sales skills

Jul 2017 - Oct 2018

ONLINE COSMETIC SHOP "MINT - TAIWAN FACE MASK"

Manager

- Reach 35.000.000 VND revenue in the first month
- Still maintain take care more than 15 loyalconsumers

Jan 2018 – Aug 2018

TOUS ACCESSORIES

Manager

- Reach 8.000.000 VND revenue in the first month
- Reach 40.000.000 VND revenue in the second month
- Strengthen sales skills, problem solving skill and task management

SOCIAL ACTIVITY

"TIEP SUC MUA THI 2014" PROJECT

Volunteer

ENROLLMENT CONSULTANCY PROJECT – "TOI LA SINH VIEN 2015& 2016"

Content Department